What’s up.
I’m gonna be using this as a test for uploading
and streaming video on 5 different free video hosting services.
When I first started this website,
I was thinking about how I would implement videos for my YouTube channels archive.
Now for me,
the answer was pretty simple.
A few years ago,
I stumbled upon a service called Abyss.to
and I found it on a Vietnamese anime dub piracy website
because I wanted to watch One Piece in Vietnamese dub.
The One Piece!
Truly always exist!
Abyss is a free video hoster with unlimited bandwidth and storage
and I've been using it since 2023 for another website
and the creation of this website here.
Abyss.to is great but my main problem with it
is the slow speeds that I've been getting.
It’s a total dealbreaker and even more
if you don’t have an adblock to block all the ads.
So because of this,
I went out of my way to “research” alternatives using AI LLMs
and these are the ones that I’ve found.
All 5 of them.
I have never used these services before,
so I am using this video as an opportunity to test and see if they work or not.
Hopefully my video doesn't get removed,
I don't get charged money or anything,
and the speeds are faster than abyss.to.